<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <!-- For exercise 2 I stuck to the same document I was looking at for the first exercise. This time, I tried to make my tags a bit more descriptive
    for example, whenever a person was mentioned in this letter, I would add the tag 'person' not matter if they were named or not. Now, if there was a person in the 
    letter that was mentioned by name, I put the tag 'namedPerson' around them. Any unnamed people kept the tag 'person.
    I also tried to focus on adding physical descriptions of the actual letter into my markup. I created the tag 'physicalCondition' so I could
    note any irregularities in the paper, like the red stains that are blotted throughout it. I also tried to note
    instances of when the author made his own changes, like crossing a word out. I also did this on my first go of this exercise,
    but I tried to be even more vigilant this time.-->
    <page num="1"><date type="1804-03-09"><place kind="capital of New York">Albany</place> March 9,
            1804</date>
        <writersEdit change="on the side of the first page in the margin there are is writing that's scribbled out"/>
        <salutations>My Dear friend</salutations> I am just going to proceed in the stage for <place
            kind="city or state">New York</place>. However, I must endeavor first to give you some
        account of my journey this far, through a country which was once the seat of your ancestors;
        but that is now covered with European settlements, whose <word interpretation="questionable"
            >persevering</word> industry has greatly changed the face of the country; and forests
        continue to disappear before the efforts of the laborious <writersEdit
            change="crossed out an e and replaced it with an a">woodman</writersEdit>. Is there any
        thing in their change to call for the sensations of sorrow in the
        breast<!-- I feel like this could also be saying the 'breath of the philanthropic patriot' -->
        of the philanthropic patriot? if there is, it is not because the inanimate clod has changed
        possessors, or that, what was once an unculti<lineBreak>-vated</lineBreak>
            waste,<writersEdit change="crossed out a word right here"/> is now covered with human
        habitations, and rendered abundant in productions for the sustenance and comfort of man; but
        it is because we have not been sufficiently benefited by the example of that which is worthy
        and commendable in the character of good Europeans <writersEdit
            change="crossed out a word right here"/> and have been greatly <physicalCondition paper="has a red stain around the area the sentences before and after this tag is written"/> 
       <interpretation mine="contamination (of?) the contrary"> contaminated to the contrary</interpretation> -
        Had the <people>Chiefs</people><physicalCondition paper="above the word 'chiefs' there is another red stain"/>, who relinquished this country, acquired more vir-tuous
        knowledge from their enlightened neighbours, they might have obtained such compensation and
        retained such <word interpretation="questionable">reserves</word> which properly disposed of
        after the settle<lineBreak>-ment</lineBreak> of the country, when the value of land had
        raised; might have enabled them to have established a fund for the support and promotion of
        industrious in our present
        territory<writersEdit change="right after he writes 'territory' there is slightly over four lines of
            writing that he has crossed out, and it is all illedgable"/>
           But to return to my journey <writersEdit added="a hypen">–</writersEdit> I left <place kind="city">Niagara</place>
        and parted with my friends with I know not what mixed impressions of joy and grief – which
        seemed to urge me with greater expedition to proceed &amp; rendered it exceeding unpleasant
        for me to make any delay. However as agree-ably as the situation of my mind would allow of,
        I passed one day at <place type="city?">Canandarque (sp. Canadaque)</place> mostly in the
        company of <namedPeople>Mr. &amp; Mrs. Morris</namedPeople> &amp; <namedPerson>Mr.
            Greig</namedPerson>, a gentleman from Scotland, who had always honored </page>
    <page num="2">(p.12) me with every hospitable and polite attention whenever business called me
        to these parts. My friend <writersEdit
            change="crossed out a word and wrote Ihaskoghsage above it"
                ><namedPerson>Ihaskoghsage</namedPerson></writersEdit> was not at home, but I
        obtained of that which was due a sufficiency to enable me to attempt my voyage from the
        gentleman who manages his affairs. At the Inn where I stop a <person>Man</person> put up who
        told me he was going the way I proposed to go and that I might obtain a passage in his
        sleigh. When he had satisfied me, that he would be expeditious, and that I might depend upon
        the goodness of his horses, I agreed to go with him. In consequence of changing my mode of
        travelling from foot to going in a carriage a young <person>lady</person> from our parts
        then at Canandarque (sp. Canadaque) with a <person>brother</person>, whom I knew proposed
        going under my protection, to <place kind="unsure">Icohare</place> where she had
            <person>another brother</person>. But unfortunately we were both deceived in the
        capability of the horses that drew us and shortly after our departure it now ap-peared
        clear, that unless we obtained others, we should be sure of a tedious journey. Had I been
        alone I would have easily remedied this inconvenience by going on foot; but as the Lady had
        come under my protection I could not with propriety leave her until we reached her brothers.
        I endeavored to hire a sleigh, but none was to be had; so we were constrained to remain with
        the old man and his sorry nags. The first day we slept at about <distance unit="mile">six
            miles</distance>
        <place>East of Cayuga</place>, and the next day at Ikanyadares, about <distance unit="miles"
            >eighteen miles</distance>farther. The snow had fallen very deep, which so increased the
        difficulty of travelling, that our man with his sleigh could hardly be prevailed on to start
        again, and all attempts to obtain another sleigh and horses were fruitless. I am
        apprehend-sive, that contrary to my inclination, my looks betrayed the anxiety of my mind at
        being detained by the tardiness of our conveyance. The lady observed she had a
            <person>brother in law</person> about <distance unit="miles">twenty six miles</distance>
        farther, and that if she could get that far, she would tarry until the roads became better –
        we set off again, but had not proceeded above five miles when our man expressed his
        determination of not going any farther. Not finding any horses to hire at the house where we
        stopped (sp. stopt), I was on my way to the next house to inquire if any might be had there,
        when I perceived</page>
</root>
