<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../ODD/out/tei_all_myImmortal.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<?xml-model href="../ODD/out/tei_all_myImmortal.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Chapters 11-12</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Originally Published on Fanfiction.net on <date when="2007-03-03">March 3rd,
                  2007</date> It was then removed by Fanfiction.net on <date when="2008-10">October
                     2008</date>for a reason that has never been confirmed.</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>born digital</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
   <text n="11">
      <front>
         <docTitle>
            <titlePart>Chapter 11</titlePart>
         </docTitle>
         <head place="top">Chapter 11. AN: i sed stup flaming up prepz! c if dis <w norm="chapter">chaptr</w> is 
            <w norm="stupid">srupid</w>!1111 it <w norm ="deals">delz</w> wit rly <w norm ="serious">sris</w> <w norm ="issues">issus</w>! <w norm ="so">sp</w> <w norm ="see">c</w> 4 urself if <w norm ="its">itz</w> <w norm ="stupid">ztupid</w> <w norm ="by the way">brw</w> fangz 2 
            ma frend raven 4 <w norm="helping">hleping</w> me!</head>
      </front>
      <body>
         <p><said who="Ebony">NO!</said> I screamed. I was  <w norm ="horrified">horrorfied</w>!
            <name ref="HG">B'loody Mary</name> tried to comfort me but I told her
            fuck off and I ran to my room crying myself.  <name ref="AD">Dumbledore</name> chased after me shouting
            but he had to stop when I went into my room cause he would look like a perv that way.</p>
         
         <p>Anyway, I started crying tears of blood and then I slit both of my wrists. 
            They got all over my clothes so I took them off and jumped into the bath angrily 
            while I put on a <rs type="band">Linkin Park</rs> song at full volume. I grabbed a <w norm="stake">steak</w> and almost stuck 
            it into my heart to commit suicide. I was so <rs type="swear">fucking</rs> depressed! 
            I got out of the bathtub and put on a <rs type="fashion">black low-cut dress with lace all over it sandly. 
               I put on black high heels with pink metal stuff on the ends and six pairs of skull earrings</rs>. 
            I couldn't <rs type="swear">fucking</rs> believe it. Then I looked out the window and screamed… 
            <name ref="SS"><w norm="Snape">Snap</w></name> was spying on me and he was taking a video tape of me! And <name ref="RL"><w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w></name> 
            was <w norm="masturbating">masticating</w> to it! 
            They were sitting on their broomsticks.</p>
         
         <p><said who="Ebony">EW, YOU <rs type="swear">FUCKING</rs> PERVS, STOP LOOKING AT ME NAKED! ARE YOU PEDOS OR WHAT</said>! 
            I screamed putting on a black towel with a picture of <name ref="MM">Marilyn Mason</name> on it.
            Suddenly <name ref="HP">Vampire</name> ran in.</p>
         
         <p><said who="Vampire">Abra Kedavra!</said> he yelled at Snape and <w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w> pointing his <w norm="wand">womb</w>. 
            I took my gun and shot Snape and <w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w> a gazillion times and they both 
            started screaming and the camera broke. Suddenly, <w norm="Dumbledore">Dumblydore</w> ran in. 
            <said who="Dumbledore">Ebony, it has been revealed that someone has - NOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</said>
            he shouted looking at Snape and <w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w> and then he waved his wand and suddenly…
             </p>
         
         <p><name ref="RH"><w norm="Hagrid">Hargrid</w></name> ran outside on his broom and said everyone we need to talk.</p>
         
         <p><said who="Dumbledore">What do you know, <w norm="Hagrid">Hargrid</w>? You're just a little Hogwarts student</said>!</p>
         <p><said who="Hagrid">I MAY BE A HOGWARTS STUDENT….</said><w norm="Hagrid">Hargirid</w> paused angrily. <said who="Hagrid">BUT I AM ALSO A SATANIST</said>!</p>
         
         <p><said who="Snape">This cannot be.</said> <w norm="Snape">Snap</w> said in a crisp voice as blood dripped from his hand where 
            <w norm="Dunbledore">Dumblydore's</w> wand had shot him. <said who="Dumbledore">There must be other factors.</said></p>
         <p><said who="Ebony">YOU DON'T HAVE ANY</said>! I yelled in madly.</p>
         <p><w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w> held up the camera <w norm="triumphantly">triumelephantly</w>. <said who="Lupin"><w norm="his">he</w> lens may be ruined but the tape is still there!</said></p>
         <p> felt faint, more than I normally do like how it feels when you do not drink enough blood.</p>
         <p><said who="Lupin">Why are you doing this?</said> <w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w> said angrily while he rubbed his dirty hands on his clook.</p>
         <p>And then I heard the words that I had heard before but not from him. 
            I did not know whether to feel shocked and happy or to bite him and drink his 
            blood because I felt faint.</p>
         <p><said who="Hagrid">BECAUSE…BECAUSE….</said> Hargid said and he paused in the air <w norm="dramatically">dramitaclly</w>, waving his wand 
            in the air. Then swooped he in singing to the tune of a gothic version of a song by 
            <name ref="CJ">50 Cent</name>.</p>
         <p><said who="Snape">Because you're <w norm="gothic">goffic</w>?</said> <w norm="Snape">Snap</w> asked in a little afraid voice cause he was <w norm="afraid">afraind </w>
            it meant he was connected with Satan.
           </p>
         <p><said who="Hagrid">Because I LOVE HER!</said></p>
      </body>
   </text>
      <text n="12">
         <front>
            <docTitle>
               <titlePart>Chapter 12</titlePart>
            </docTitle>
         </front>
         <body>
            <p><note place="top">AN: stop <w norm="flaming">f,aing</w> ok <w norm="Hagrid">hargrid</w> is a pedo <w norm="to">2</w> a lot of ppl in 
                  <w norm="American">amerikan</w> <w norm="schools">skoolz</w> <w norm="are">r</w> <w norm="like">lik</w> dat
                  I <w norm="wanted">wunted</w> <w norm="to">2</w> <w norm="address">adres</w> <w norm="the">da</w> <w norm="issue">ishu</w>! how 
                  <w norm="do">du</w> <w norm="you">u</w> <w norm="know">no</w> <w norm="Snape">snap</w> <w norm="isn't">iant</w> <w norm="Christian">kristian</w> plus hargrid isn't 
                  really in  <w norm="love">luv</w>  <w norm="with">wif</w> ebony <w norm="that">dat</w> was  <name ref="CD"> <w norm="Cedric">sedric</w></name> ok!</note></p>
            
            <p>I was about to slit my wrists again with the silver knife that <w norm="Draco">Drago</w> had given me 
               in case anything happened to him. He had told me to use it valiantly against an 
               enemy but I knew that we must both go together.</p>
            <p><said who="Ebony">NO</said>! I THOUGHT IT WAS <w norm="Hagrid">HAIRgrid</w> but it was Vampire. He started to scream. 
               <said who="Vampire"><rs type="swear">OMFG</rs>! NOOOOO! MY SCAR HURTS!</said> and then….. his eyes rolled up! 
               You could only see his red whites.</p>
            <p>I stopped. <said who="Ebony">How did <w norm="you">u</w> know</said>?</p>
            
            <p><said who="Vampire">I saw it! And my scar turned back into the lightning bolt</said>!</p>
            
            <p><said who="Ebony">NO!</said> I ran up closer. <said who="Ebony">I thought you didn't have a scar anymore</said>! I shouted.</p>
            
            <p><said who="Vampire">I do but <name ref="RW">Diabolo</name> changed it into a pentagram for me and I always cover it up 
               with foundation.</said> he said back.<said who="Vampire">Anyway my scar hurt and it turned back into 
               the lightning bolt! Save me! then I had a vision of what was happening to Draco….
                  <w norm="Voldemort">Volfemort</w> has him bondage!</said></p>
            
            <p>Anyway I was in the school nurse's office now recovering from my slit wrists. 
               <w norm="Snape">Snap</w> and <w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w> and <w norm="Hagrid">HAHRID</w> were there too. They were going to St. <w norm="Mungo's">Mango's</w> after 
               they recovered cause they were pedofiles and you can't have those <rs type="swear">fucking</rs> pervs 
               teaching in a school with lots of hot <w norm="girls">gurlz</w>. Dumbledore had constipated the 
               cideo camera they took of me naked. I put up my middle finger at them.</p>
            
            <p>Anyway <w norm="Hagrid">Hargrid</w> came into my hospital bed holding a bouquet of pink roses.</p>
            <p><said who="Hagrid"><w norm="Ebony">Enoby</w> I need to tell <w norm="you">u</w> somethnig.</said> he said in a <w norm="very">v</w>. 
               serious voice, giving me the roses.</p>
            <p><said who="Ebony"><rs type="swear">Fuck</rs> off.</said> I told him. <said who="Ebony">You know I <rs type="swear">fucking</rs> hate the color pink anyway, and 
                  I don't like fucked up preps like you.</said> I snapped. Hargrid had been mean to 
               me before for being <w norm="gothic">gottik</w>.</p>
            
            <p><said who="Hagrid">No <w norm="Ebony">Enoby</w>.</said> <w norm="Hagrid">Hargrid</w> says. <said who="Hagrid">Those are not roses</said>.</p>
            
            <p><said who="Ebony">What, are they <w norm="goths">goffs</w> too you poser prep?</said> I asked cause I was angry that he had 
               brought me pink roses.</p>
            
            <p><said who="Hagrid">I saved your life!</said> He yelled angrily. <said who="Ebony">No you didn't I replied.</said> 
               <said who="Hagrid">You saved me from getting a <name ref="PH">Paris Hilton</name> p- video made from your shower 
                  scene and being <w norm="viewed">vued</w> by <w norm="Snape">Snap</w> and <w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w>. Who <w norm="Masturbated">MASTABATED</w> </said>
               <note place="parenthesis">(<w norm="see">c</w> is <w norm="that">dat</w> <w norm="spelt">speld</w> <w norm="wrong">rong</w>)</note> 
               to it he added silently.</p>
            
            
            <p><said who="Ebony">Whatever!</said> I yelled angirly.</p>
            
            <p>He pointed his wand at the pink roses. <said who="Hagrid">These aren't roses.</said> He suddenly 
               looked at them with an evil look in his eye and muttered 
               <lg><l>Well If you wanted 
                     Honesty that's all you haD TO SAY!</l>
               </lg>.</p>
            <p><said who="Ebony">That's not a spell that's an <rs type="band">MCR</rs> song.</said> I corrected him wisely.</p>
            <p><said who="Hagrid">I know, I was just warming up my vocal <w norm="cords">cordes</w>.</said> Then he screamed. 
               <said who="Hagrid">Petulus merengo mi kremicli romacio <note place="parenthesis">(<w norm="for">4</w> all <w norm="you">u</w> cool <w norm="gothic">goffic</w> mcr fans out, there, 
                     that is a tribute! specially for <name ref="R"></name>raven I love you girl!)</note>imo noto okayo!</said></p>
            <p>And then the roses turned into a huge black flame floating in the middle of the air. 
               And it was black. Now I knew he wasn't a prep.</p>
            <p><said who="Ebony">OK I believe you now <rs type="swear">wtf</rs> is <w norm="Draco">Drako</w>?</said></p>
            <p><w norm="Hagrid">Hairgrid</w> rolled his eyes. I looked into the balls of flame but I could <w norm="see">c</w> nothing.</p>
            <p><said who="Hagrid"><w norm="you">U</w> <w norm="see">c</w>, <w norm="Ebony">Enobby</w>,</said> <w norm="Dumnledore">Dumblydore</w> said, watching the two of us watching the flame. 
               <said who="Dumbledore"><w norm="to">2</w> <w norm="see">c</w> <w norm="what">wht</w> <w norm="is">iz</w> <w norm="and">n</w> <w norm="the">da</w> 
                  <w norm="flames">flmes</w><note place="parenthesis">(HAHA <w norm="you">U</w> <w norm="reviewer's">REVIEWRS</w> FLAMES <w norm="get it">GEDDIT</w>)</note> 
                  u<w norm="must">mst</w> find <w norm="yourself">urslf</w> 1st, <w norm="ok">k</w>?</said></p>
            
            <p><said who="Hagrid">I HAVE FOUND MYSELF OK YOU MEAN OLD MAN!</said> <w norm="Hagrid">Hargrid</w> yelled. <w norm ="Dumbledore">dUMBLydore</w> <w norm="looked">lookd</w> shockd.
               I guess he didn't have a headache or else he would have said something back.</p>
            
            <p><w norm="Hagrid">Hairgrid</w> stormed off back into his bed. <said who="Hagrid"><w norm="you">U</w> <w norm="are">r</w> a liar, prof <w norm="dumbledore">dumbledoree</w>!</said></p>
            
            <p>Anyway when I got better I went upstairs and put on a <rs type="fashion">black leather minidress that 
               was all ripped on the ends with lace on it. There was some corset stuff on the front. 
               Then I put on black fishnets and black high-heeled boots with pictures of 
               <name ref="BA">Billie Joe Armstrong</name> on them. I put my hair all out around me so I looked 
                  like <rs type="movieCharacter">Samara</rs> from the Ring <note place="parenthesis">(if <w norm="you">u</w> don't know who she <w norm="is">iz</w> <w norm="your">ur</w> a prep so <rs type="swear"><w norm="fuck">fuk</w></rs> off!)</note> 
               and I put on blood-red lipstick, black eyeliner and black lip gloss.</rs></p>
            
            <p><said who="Bloody Mary">You look <w norm="cute"><w norm="kawaii">kawai</w></w>, girl.</said> B'loody Mary said sadly. <said who="Ebony">fangs <note place="parenthesis">(geddit)</note> you do too.</said>
               I said sadly too, but I was still upset. I slit both of my wrists feeling totally 
               depressed and I sucked all the blood. I cried again in my bathroom and put the shades 
               on so <w norm="Snape">Snap</w> and <w norm="Lupin">Loopin</w> couldn't spy on me this time. I went to some classes. 
               Vampire was in the <w norm="care">Hair</w> of Magical Magic Creatures. He looked all depressed because 
               Draco had disappeared and he had used to be in love with Draco. He was sucking some 
               blood from a Hufflepuff.</p>
            
            <p><said who="Draco">Hi</said>. he said in a depressed way. <said who="Ebony">Hi back.</said> I said in an <w norm="equally">wqually</w> said way.</p>
            
            <p>We both looked at each other for some time. Harry had beautiful red gothic 
               eyes so much like Dracos. Then… we jumped on each other and started screwing 
               each other.</p>
            <p><said who="Mcgonagol">STOP IT NOW YOU HORNY SIMPLETONS!</said> shouted <name ref="MM">Professor <w norm="Mcgonagol">McGoggle</w></name> who was 
               watching us and so was everyone else.</p>
            <p><said who="Ebony">Vampire you <rs type="swear">fucker</rs>!</said> I said slapping him. <said who="Ebony">Stop trying to screw me. 
                You know I loved Draco! </said> I shouted and then I ran away angrily.</p>
            <p>Just then he started to scream. <said who="Vampire">OMFG! NOOOOO! MY SCAR HURTS!</said> and then….. 
               his eyes rolled up! You could only see his red whites.</p>
            <p><said who="Ebony">NO!</said> I ran up closer.</p>
            <p><said who="Ebony">I thought you didn't have a scar anymore!</said> I shouted.</p>
            <p><said who="Vampire">I do but Diabolo changed it into a pentagram for me and I always cover it up 
                  with foundation.</said> he said back. <said who="Vampire">Anyway my scar hurt and then I had a vision 
                     of what was happening to Draco….<name ref="TR"><w norm="Voldemort">Volfemort</w></name> has him bondage!</said></p>
            <p><note place="bottom">SPECIAL FANGZ <w norm="to">2</w> RAVEN MY <w norm="gothic">GOFFIX</w> BLOOD <w norm="sister">SISTA</w> <w norm="what the fuck">WTF</w> <w norm="you're">UR</w> 
                  <w norm="supposed">SUPPOZD</w> <w norm="to">2</w> <w norm="read">RIT</w> <w norm="this">DIS</w>!11111111 HEY RAVEN DO <w norm="you">U</w> KNOW WHERE MY SWEATER <w norm="is">I</w></note></p>
            <p></p>
         </body>
         
      </text>
</TEI>
