<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="recipeRelax.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<root>
    <title>Shrewsbury Cakes: Original Recipe.</title>
<context>This recipe comes from <source>MS Codex 625</source>, a manuscript recipe book 
that belonged to a student in a London cooking school in the early eighteenth century. 
The pastry school was owned by <person>Edward Kidder</person>, who taught at a few locations 
    in <city>London</city> between around <date type="year"> 1720</date> and <date type="year">1734</date>. Blank books with printed title pages 
seem to have been used by students to write down recipes they learned.
Kidder also published his recipes in the printed volume, 
    <book>Receipts for Pastry and Cookery</book>, in <date type="year">1720</date>.
</context>
<ogrecipe>Take a <measurement>pound</measurement> of fresh <ingredient type="dairy">butter</ingredient> a <measurement>pound </measurement> of double
    <ingredient type= "bakery">refind sugar sifted fine</ingredient> a <measurement>little </measurement>beaten
    <ingredient type="spice">mace</ingredient> &amp; <quantity>4</quantity> <ingredient> eggs</ingredient> 
    <!-- I put an ingredient tage without the grocery section for the eggs because usually eggs will be in the 
    egg section of the grocery store and writing "ingredient= egg" seemed goofy-->
   <action>beat them all together with.
your hands till tis very leight &amp; looks
curdling</action> you put thereto a <measurement>pound &amp; 1/2 </measurement> of
    <ingredient type= "bakery">flower</ingredient> <action><modern word="roll">roul</modern> them out into little cakes</action></ogrecipe>

<newRecipe>Our recipe (halved from the original)

<callsFor>1/2 lb. (2 sticks) butter, softened
1/2 lb. sugar
1/2 tsp. cinnamon 
2 eggs
3/4 lb. flour</callsFor>

Using an <tool>electric mixer</tool>, <action step="1">cream together the butter and sugar. </action>
    Then add the <ingredient>eggs</ingredient> and <action step="2">mix at medium speed until the mixture looks curdled. </action>
    <action step="3">Sift together dry ingredients</action> and <action step="4">add at low speed until just combined. </action> 
    <action step="5">Scoop and roll the dough by hand into <measurement>1-tbsp</measurement>. balls, then pat flat.</action>
<suggestion>[You could also refrigerate the dough until it’s firm enough to roll out 
    on a flat surface and cut out into rounds.]</suggestion>

Bake at <measurement>350F</measurement> for <time>15-18 minutes </time> 
    <suggestion>(ours were about 1/3″ thick, so you could roll them thinner 
and have a slightly shorter cooking time)</suggestion>. They’re done once they turn the 
slightest bit brown around the edges. This halved recipe yielded about two dozen cookies.

The Results

<suggestion>If you like snickerdoodles (and who doesn’t?), you’d like these. 
We added the cinnamon because we like it and couldn’t resist, and we thought it rounded out the mace nicely. 
These are mild, fairly soft cookies that are great with tea. We rolled and patted 
the dough into individual cookies because it was too soft and stick to roll out, 
but a little bit more flour and a stint in the fridge might make the dough easier 
to work with a rolling pin.</suggestion></newRecipe>
</root>
